export const sections = [
    {
      title: 'Section 1',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'Question 1.1?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option A'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 1.2?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option B'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 1.3?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option C'
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      title: 'Section 2',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'Question 2.1?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option D'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 2.2?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option E'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 2.3?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option A'
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      title: 'Section 3',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'Question 3.1?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option B'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 3.2?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option C'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 3.3?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option D'
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      title: 'Section 4',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'Question 4.1?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option E'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 4.2?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option A'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 4.3?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option B'
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      title: 'Section 5',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'Question 5.1?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option C'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 5.2?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option D'
        },
        {
          question: 'Question 5.3?',
          options: ['Option A', 'Option B', 'Option C', 'Option D', 'Option E'],
          correctAnswer: 'Option E'
        }
      ]
    }
  ];
  